All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
It's sleeping! Look! The Noah's not headed toward the island anymore!
The Princess is leading it away from us! It won't crash into us after all!
Don't let it hurt you!
Swim faster!
If I'm going to steer the Noah clear of the bubble, then I have to swim as far out to sea as I can!
But one teeny tiny little magic word can spare you this dread fate, and that's yes! Simply utter that one word and your troubles will be over!
I'm deeply sorry, Sir Decken, but I simply can't do that!
Why must you refuse to marry me?!
Because you're not my type!
Ah! What the hell with you?!
You need to learn how to treat a lady, or anybody for that matter!
Shirahoshi is our baby sister! We will never let you lay a hand on her! Not ever!
You came to save me! And Hoa is here as well! Thank you!
I also regret being suspicious of you at first.
Ah, it's no big deal. Let's head to the deck!
Bah-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Goodness, if it isn't Horny Jones!
Say, whatever happened to Neptune? Dead, maybe?
By the way, I'm using the Noah to torture Shirahoshi as we speak!
A genius idea on my part! Don't you think, brother?
It's not bad, but I think I've got an even better idea.
Do you now? Well, let's hear it!
Actually, it's better if I show you.
If you died, what would become of this ship?
Well, Dakin?
The fierce fight begins! Luffy vs. Hordy!
Dakin?
Horty, you've made a terrible mistake.
I've just touched you with my left hand!
You turned your back on me!
As I recall, Deacon, you started this yourself.
You know, to be honest, I was a bit nervous when I first saw the shadow of the Noah looming over Fishman Island.
But after I thought about it, breaking the bubble didn't seem like such a bad idea.
Fishman Island would be wiped out, but we'd still have the Fishman District.
And if you die, here and now, then your Markmark power will deactivate, right?
Then the ship will come crashing down right onto that useless kingdom.
Then nothing will remain.
What I want most, right now, is to take care of all those meddlesome straw-had pirates.
For good.
True, I stand to lose, well, thousands.
But it'll be easy enough for me to pick up all the human slaves I want later on.
Thousands will die, huh?
I like that.
Why don't we start...
With you!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Die for new Fishman Island.
We'll be sure to remember you.
I will berry it.
Thin ...
...
You'll be dead before long, and then the great ship Noah will begin its descent, bringing
my wrath upon this wretched land.
You know, I'm a kind man, so just for you, maybe I should make your beloved join you in death.
Your time has come, princess.
He stabbed him!
First they're pals, now they're shooking each other off!
No time to worry about that now!
Look out!
Here he comes!
We'll stop you, Arnie!
Oh yeah, not likely.
You're not the ones I left.
Whoa!
Dear brothers, no!
Run!
You have to get out of here right now!
Alright!
This'll be easy now that you've left the safety of the hardshell tower, twin sis.
You're fine!
You're fine.
What a pity.
You're kind of the world's fastest swimmers,
but with this power, I'm faster.
Ah!
Help me!
SHAR kah opponents!
THEY PLAY HALL F pins!
Ah!
Come comeonton!
Thank goodness! I'm so glad you're here!
Brother!
And Straw Hat too?
That's right. This time, we won't lose so easily.
Of course.
Meanwhile, at Fishman Island's Conchcord Plaza...
Captain Vanderdeck doesn't like me anymore, so he's left me here to die!
That's the brakes! You're just one more thing I have to sacrifice in my pursuit of Shilohoshi!
Quit trying and fight, you big baby!
Yeah, you're the only one big enough to beat up the Kraken!
I know you can win, Tsurume!
Come on, kick his butt!
But he's almost the same size as the Kraken, so I wonder why he's so scared to fight him.
Well, I wouldn't want to.
Uh, there, there. Perhaps you didn't hear correctly.
He didn't say sacrifice. He said, uh, some help would be nice.
Huh?
You didn't really think he would destroy the island and leave you to your death, did you?
But... he did say I was gonna die!
He was just saying you should fight, as though you were prepared to die.
Really?
Tell him.
Uh, uh, yeah! Totally!
He's lucky his captain trusts him with something so important!
That's great!
What a big boy!
Uh, what he means is you're strong!
Oh! Now I get it!
I don't think you do.
Anyway, this is for you.
I want you to take it so you can help us defeat those mean old straw hats, okay?
That's an energy steroid!
Wait a sec.
How's it gonna work on somebody that big?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
What the?
It works!
Extra well!
Gah!
Aaaaahhh!
Ah!
Gah!
Sui-me!
I'm sorry, Captain!
I should have trusted you all along!
Nice work!
That stupid squid is history now!
Hey, are you okay there, buddy?
Oh no, he's unconscious!
Time for!
You do!
He's not even the same person anymore!
The Captain will be so proud of me!
Gah!
Who's next?
Uh, I think he said to kill that guy!
The,Dude?
Ok!
Ahhhhhhh!
Who next?
I think he said to kill that guy.
The blue dude?
Okay!
Jinbei, behind you!
Fishman Karate!
7,000 brick!
Groundhouse kick!
It was fantastic ourselves.
Ouch!
This is why I tighten you extreme.
What's the big deal?!
vaak
Ah, no, no!
Nami! There's a lady here!
Keep those butt shockwaves to yourself, you creep!
That's it, pal!
No! That Haradou just hit me!
Here's the deal!
If you put so much as a single scratch on our beautiful map goddess,
then I'll put another gap in your team!
What? Why are all his kicks working so well?
I don't know if this guy is crazy strong or the giant guy is crazy weak!
Oh, great!
Huh?
Now I'm all dirty!
It wasn't my fault! That guy knocked me over!
You want to fight? Then fight me!
I want a piece of you too!
You big dumpling!
Okay, but leave us out of here!
Meal floor!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Hyozo, come help us fight! We need you!
Octopus, please. Make it snappy, okay?
Does this place look like a bar to you?
Besides, isn't that like cannibalism?
Don't be such a drag!
It's too late! He's already passed out!
Honestly, what a pathetic display!
Hmm?
This is my chance.
If I prove myself, then I might become an officer in just one move.
Ah!
No, no, no!
I see!
You're far too crafty to fall for surprise attack!
Who the hell are you?
I'm the soon to be number one fishman swordsman!
I am the incomparable Noodle!
I see. You're far too crafty to fall for surprise attack.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the soon to be number one fishman swordsman.
I am the Incomfortable Noodle!
A hangover? What should we do?
He's freaking out!
You're far more skilled than I thought.
And you're no good at all.
You'll change your mind once you see the light.
Oh, I'm blind!
Good luck dodging my attacks now that you can't use your eyes!
Farewell!
I'm blind!
Good luck dodging my attacks now that you can't use your eyes!
Farewell!
You only see with your eyes?
Some swordsman you are.
Get lost!
You just got lucky that time.
I'm destined to be the number one swordsman and I'll cut down anyone who stands in my way.
Well then, you've got a long way to go.
Not again!
We told you we're on your side!
What new level of drunk is this?
I don't know, but I'm scared.
He's stronger than usual.
Get ready.
Tottering.
He cut the net like paper!
I don't get it.
He was writhing in pain and then he changed color.
Yeah, I don't get it either, but that's exactly what happened to Horty when he transformed.
At least Horty had the decency not to swing swords at us.
Oh, this feels good.
So much energy.
Let's see.
Now, who should I butcher next?
Don't be shy!
What do we do now?
He's not going to quit slashing until somebody stops him!
Oh, come on.
Who's it going to be?
Huh?
This is just way too many swords.
Finally, a worthy opponent.
That last guy was too easy.
Hold on.
You heard me.
I'm calling dibs on him.
We might as well get a warm-up before we go to the new world.
Should be fun.
That sucks.
I guess it's not as strong underwater.
Not as strong?
Tough luck.
Look, give it up already.
We're thousands of meters underwater, you fool.
You can fight, but there's no way in hell you're going to win.
Not against a fish man.
See?
Either way, the whole island is doomed.
That includes your friends, the princess, and everyone else down there.
You're just a weakling.
Get it?
You can't protect anyone.
Watch me.
I'll save them all.
I trained for two years.
I'm ready.
The Straw Hat Pirates go head-to-head with the powerful officers from Horty's crew.
Thanks to their two years of training, they hold their own with a flurry of new fighting techniques.
However, their struggle will all be for naught if Luffy cannot find a way to overcome Horty and stop the Noah from crushing Fishman Island.
On the next, One Piece.
A massive, confused fight.
The Straw Hats versus the new Fishman Pirates.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.
The força.
The worms fight.
The